hitid,workerid,raw_json
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,635181926521b3fcfcbc011d,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '48', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-09T01:54:27.807Z'}, '2': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': []}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': []}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': []}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': []}, '6': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '63', 'q5': 'asdasd', 'q6': 'asdasd'}, 'workerId': '635181926521b3fcfcbc011d', 'assignmentId': '0yq2ojzzx91f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-09T01:55:12.038Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,635181926521b3fcfcbc011d,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '38', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '1': 'Generate Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-14T18:43:05.962Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'telescope', 'time': '2024-07-14T18:43:11.694Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'magnifying glass', 'time': '2024-07-14T18:43:23.083Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 2, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'doorstop', 'time': '2024-07-14T18:45:57.939Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 3, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'garage sale tool', 'time': '2024-07-14T18:48:48.441Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 4, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'makeshift flag', 'time': '2024-07-14T18:50:13.695Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '56', 'q5': 'n/a', 'q6': 'no'}, 'workerId': '635181926521b3fcfcbc011d', 'assignmentId': '0yq2ojzzx91f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-14T18:52:27.060Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,635181926521b3fcfcbc011d,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '69', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-14T20:29:39.310Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'makeshift flag', 'time': '2024-07-14T20:29:44.390Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 1, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'hula hoop', 'time': '2024-07-14T20:32:51.262Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': []}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 2, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'doorstop', 'time': '2024-07-14T20:36:49.048Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '55', 'q5': 'yes', 'q6': 'yes'}, 'workerId': '635181926521b3fcfcbc011d', 'assignmentId': '0yq2ojzzx91f', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-14T21:21:09.535Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,5ef6fed00ea7fe4063853e8c,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '80', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:10:00.118Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'swing set', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:07.163Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'building blocks', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:18.441Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'outdoor seating', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:45.415Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'wall', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:24.472Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'garden planter', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:32.492Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'sandbox', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:57.561Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 6, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'flip it over and make a blanket fort', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:14.647Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'raised platform bed', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:30.889Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'whiteboard or chalkboard', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:36.513Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'pool table', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:41.861Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 10, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'wall decoration', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:15.312Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'drinking vessel', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:20.852Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'plant pot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:24.127Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'footprint painting', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:34.096Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'trophy', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:51.716Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'memento', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:55.583Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'lamp', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:35.843Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 17, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'musical instrument', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:12.573Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'plant pot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:15.335Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'heat and turn into another shape to use as hourglass', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:29.486Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'ship in a bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:40.759Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'store paper stars inside', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:45.534Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'storage vessel', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:52.426Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'flower vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:57.520Z'}, {'id': 24, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'message in a bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:07.889Z'}, {'id': 25, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'ampoule', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:28.951Z'}, {'id': 26, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'spray bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:31.798Z'}, {'id': 27, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'alcohol storage', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:41.970Z'}, {'id': 28, 'iid': 11, 'name': 'broken glass art', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:51.215Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '40', 'q5': 'I think of DIY arts and crafts that I would do with the bottle.', 'q6': 'No.'}, 'workerId': '5ef6fed00ea7fe4063853e8c', 'assignmentId': '669da30c8ef1aabaaafac82a', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:20:00.408Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,669d0936c4572e0c86f53d83,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '50', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:08:55.219Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'leg warmers', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:09:20.086Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'arm warmers', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:09:27.414Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'storage', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:09:31.441Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'protection', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:09:39.548Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'bag', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:08.717Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'backpack', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:14.182Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'overalls', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:19.759Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 7, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'ring toss', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:00.701Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:03.937Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'storage', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:07.741Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'toothbrush holder', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:12.010Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'water bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:19.316Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'rolling pin', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:29.322Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'wine bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:02.387Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 14, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'desk', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:00.391Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'fort', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:03.037Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'protection', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:09.390Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'homework station', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:14.097Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'kitchen table', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:26.665Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'dinner table', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:39.484Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'shield', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:13.360Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 21, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'dog toy', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:04.982Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'shoe', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:08.008Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'running shoe', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:11.560Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': '3', 'q4': '37', 'q5': 'Just based on what first popped in my head', 'q6': 'No'}, 'workerId': '669d0936c4572e0c86f53d83', 'assignmentId': '669da2d98ef1aabaaafac81e', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:20:27.017Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,65c266bb091c0f2811ab8d80,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '40', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '1': 'Generate Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:10:39.689Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Flower pot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:55.767Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Door stopper', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:59.234Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'Lamp base', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:06.461Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': ' Tissue box', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:21.292Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'filled with concrete and used as an anchor', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:40.020Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'Beer coozie', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:01.520Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:27.954Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 7, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'flower bed', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:47.001Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'swing', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:50.634Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'raised vegetable bed', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:17.434Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'lined with vinyl and used as a water feature', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:38.325Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'hidey hole for critters in the yard', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:52.165Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'filled with concrete and used as a weight for a backyard canopy', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:29.350Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'bird bath', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:34.036Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 14, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:45.935Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'decorative light', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:05.325Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'meat tenderizer', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:12.751Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'rolling pin', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:23.903Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'emergency candle holder', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:45.456Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'fruit fly trap', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:05.955Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 6, 'name': '""boogeyman catcher"" to help kids sleep', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:41.741Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 21, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'shelter', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:54.446Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'boat for a game of pretend', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:03.137Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'sled', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:14.525Z'}, {'id': 24, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'flipped upside down, wrapped with packing shrink wrap, and used to grow potatoes', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:57.210Z'}, {'id': 25, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'flipped on the side and used as a hiding spot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:16.813Z'}, {'id': 26, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'covered with sheet for a tent', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:42.368Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'Equally excited and concerned', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '40', 'q5': 'I thought about what I might use it for.', 'q6': 'no'}, 'workerId': '65c266bb091c0f2811ab8d80', 'assignmentId': '669da3045a8279d758645827', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:20:42.318Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,5cfbca108483c6001530c04a,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '70', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More excited than concerned'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:10:47.667Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': ' and use it as a little playhouse for a pair like a mouse or a guinea pig I used to do that they love running through objects and I feel this will be a very core ideacut the toes out of the shoeA shoe could be used for collecting water if you have no other object to collect water with you could use a shoe maybe line it with some form of plastic and then use it as a drinking utensil this would be a good idea you could also', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:26.367Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:28.917Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:35.825Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:38.921Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 4, 'iid': 0, 'name': "" go as Mitchell entire man or something strange like thatyou could also wear it as a Halloween outfit androtations with the heaviest objects and see if you can be the recordtry to get the mosttry to get the world record for Hula hoop put it around your waistyou could alsothis would be a good ideayou could sit on it it could be very comfortableseat in the garden or in your hometype ofcut it in half and use it as aA rubber tyre can be used as a planter in a garden you couldn't fill it up with dirt and use it to plant flowers in to grow or you can do something very unusual and maybe"", 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:39.370Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 5, 'iid': 0, 'name': ""You could cover this in green felt and use it as a snooker or pool table you could also use it as a very large dining table which it probably is or a desk for a computer or a gaming setup you could also use this for a secret Hideaway, you can put a piece of material over the top and use as a tent for you and your kids to play dungeons and dragons it would be fantastic. You could also use this as a bed if you put some kind of foam on it to make it comfortable and get some blankets you could kind of have a bunk bed one person sleeping on top and one person sleeping underneath. You could also use it upside down tie some rope around each leg and use as a tiny little boxing ring for your kids to have a little play fight in if they're into sport like boxing."", 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:29.322Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 1, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:31.925Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 7, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'You could use a bottle to put a message in and then chuck it in the sea to see if one day someone will retrieve it and get to read your message. You could also use it as an ornament you could put some LEDs into it and then put a cork into the top and use it as a light up bottle display in a bar or a man cave it would be really cool. You could also obviously make drinks in it but you could experiment with different types of flavours and see what concoctions you can come up with. You can also tie it to a piece of rope and then maybe tighter to a tree and Chuck stones it to see if you can smash it but obviously be safe when doing so. ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:28.018Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 1, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:33.774Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '83', 'q5': ""I just let my mind run wild. I didn't try to control what I was saying I just typed whatever I fall first in my head."", 'q6': ""I didn't have any technical issues apart from not being able to control the snake in the mid-section game""}, 'workerId': '5cfbca108483c6001530c04a', 'assignmentId': '669da2fc1322c7f64ccab2ec', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:21:01.538Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,669bbfcf3c058df5b00aee2b,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '75', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:10:24.512Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Kids toy. A kid can roll inside of it down a hill', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:49.709Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'It can be used as a plate ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:56.009Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'It can be repurposed as a chair', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:12.629Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 3, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'The glass can be repurposed to make glasses', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:36.457Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'You can put a model ship in the bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:46.240Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'It can be used as a childs piggy bank', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:58.096Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'it can be used for a collection of various bottles', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:11.976Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'The glass can be recycled', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:27.794Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'You can put a lightbulb in it', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:40.217Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 9, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'The shoe can be a bed for a pet hamster or rat', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:39.544Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'You can put dirt in it to make it suitable for bird eggs', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:53.488Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'The rubber can be used for a gaming controller', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:06.824Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'you can throw a pair of shoes over a electrical tower', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:54.032Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 13, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'It can be used as a desk', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:40.320Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'It can be used as a footstool', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:53.095Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'You can make a makeshift skateboard with the part s', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:10.887Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': '5', 'q4': '69', 'q5': 'I just tried to think of the weirdest things the items can be used for ', 'q6': 'No'}, 'workerId': '669bbfcf3c058df5b00aee2b', 'assignmentId': '669da2ef167bc8c1e18b661c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:21:13.811Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,669bbfcf3c058df5b00aee2b,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '75', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'Equally excited and concerned'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:10:24.512Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Kids toy. A kid can roll inside of it down a hill', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:10:49.709Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'It can be used as a plate ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:56.009Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'It can be repurposed as a chair', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:12.629Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 3, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'The glass can be repurposed to make glasses', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:36.457Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'You can put a model ship in the bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:46.240Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'It can be used as a childs piggy bank', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:58.096Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'it can be used for a collection of various bottles', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:11.976Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'The glass can be recycled', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:27.794Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'You can put a lightbulb in it', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:40.217Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 9, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'The shoe can be a bed for a pet hamster or rat', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:39.544Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'You can put dirt in it to make it suitable for bird eggs', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:53.488Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'The rubber can be used for a gaming controller', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:06.824Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'you can throw a pair of shoes over a electrical tower', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:54.032Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 13, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'It can be used as a desk', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:40.320Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'It can be used as a footstool', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:53.095Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'You can make a makeshift skateboard with the part s', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:10.887Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, '8': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': '5', 'q4': '69', 'q5': 'I just tried to think of the weirdest things the items can be used for ', 'q6': 'No'}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Very difficult', 'q2': 'More excited than concerned', 'q3': '5', 'q4': '69', 'q5': 'I just tried to think of the weirdest things the items can be used for ', 'q6': 'No'}, 'workerId': '669bbfcf3c058df5b00aee2b', 'assignmentId': '669da2ef167bc8c1e18b661c', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:21:14.018Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,5d02ceaaa0fcd500183ea67e,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '47', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:11:28.964Z'}, '2': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Surf board', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:11:53.796Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Dog', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:02.437Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'vegetable dryer', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:19.862Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'Cricket stump', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:46.830Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'bench', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:59.327Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'sledge', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:13.630Z'}]}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 6, 'iid': 0, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:30.069Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'whistle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:46.814Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'bottle garden', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:55.485Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'weapon', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:02.158Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'light shade', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:13.478Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:20.734Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'ship in a bottle', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:31.630Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'glass brick', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:47.974Z'}, {'id': 14, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'telescope', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:57.566Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 9, 'name': 'ornament with sand', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:07.854Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 10, 'name': 'roller blade', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:25.758Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 17, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'sail', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:41.262Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'wind sock', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:48.918Z'}, {'id': 19, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'any other item of clothing', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:00.078Z'}, {'id': 20, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'bandage', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:10.478Z'}, {'id': 21, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'choker', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:22.102Z'}, {'id': 22, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'duster', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:32.190Z'}, {'id': 23, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'mop', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:39.958Z'}, {'id': 24, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'tie to tie things together', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:02.622Z'}, {'id': 25, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'rope', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:16.862Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 26, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'ear muffs', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:47.191Z'}, {'id': 27, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'string for conkers', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:57.047Z'}, {'id': 28, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'door stop', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:05.903Z'}, {'id': 29, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'missile', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:13.847Z'}, {'id': 30, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'hammer', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:21.032Z'}, {'id': 31, 'iid': 5, 'name': 'trip hazzard', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:28.967Z'}, {'id': 32, 'iid': 6, 'name': 'reflector', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:40.799Z'}, {'id': 33, 'iid': 7, 'name': 'cushion', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:58.895Z'}, {'id': 34, 'iid': 8, 'name': 'home for mice', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:07.135Z'}]}, '6': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '30', 'q5': 'no strategy - whatever came into my head.', 'q6': 'only the snake game!'}, 'workerId': '5d02ceaaa0fcd500183ea67e', 'assignmentId': '669da314c2d02f707d97e368', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:21:58.817Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,5da39d242a298b0012cd4393,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '10', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': 'Coach Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:12:34.592Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'seat', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:50.952Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'flower pot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:12:55.623Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'book case', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:14.384Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'foot rest', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:25.891Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 4, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:26.730Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 5, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'play castle roof', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:55.382Z'}, {'id': 6, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'a small bed', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:15:04.934Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'a pontoon over a marsh', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:01.458Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'a sledge', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:14.360Z'}, {'id': 9, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'a small door', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:25.417Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 10, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'arms for inflatable wavey hands man', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:11.781Z'}, {'id': 11, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'gauntlets ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:37.473Z'}, {'id': 12, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'a play house for gerbils', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:08.085Z'}, {'id': 13, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'tie the legs and hold vegetables in it', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:18:34.392Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 14, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'plant pot', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:47.044Z'}, {'id': 15, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'drinks holder ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:05.136Z'}, {'id': 16, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'rodent home', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:34.688Z'}, {'id': 17, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'gloves', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:59.651Z'}, {'id': 18, 'iid': 4, 'name': 'emergency floatation device', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:21:33.915Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '5', 'q4': '10', 'q5': 'thinking what fits inside', 'q6': 'no'}, 'workerId': '5da39d242a298b0012cd4393', 'assignmentId': '669da3738f347e772c21a716', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:23:05.388Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,669d3ffda05541243f50451f,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '71', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': 'Generate Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:12:09.634Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:13:08.384Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Table', 'Response': [{'id': 1, 'iid': 0, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:14:26.257Z'}, {'id': 2, 'iid': 1, 'name': '', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:16:07.665Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 3, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'chair', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:15.545Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'table', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:31.818Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'slipper', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:17:47.978Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 6, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Jogging', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:04.679Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Hiking', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:14.908Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'street football', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:21:12.741Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat difficult', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '60', 'q5': 'To be fast in identify the objects', 'q6': 'No'}, 'workerId': '669d3ffda05541243f50451f', 'assignmentId': '669da2d6a05541243f505ca1', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:23:58.025Z'}"
668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a,664333b896d50fdfc656419d,"{'0': {'How Creative?': '100', 'Increased AI use makes you feel': 'More concerned than excited'}, '1': 'Generate Immediate', '2': {'PageLoad': '2024-07-22T00:19:24.862Z'}, '3': {'Prompt': 'Shoe', 'Response': [{'id': 0, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Hand warmers', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:19:46.094Z'}, {'id': 1, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Plant pots', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:20:36.861Z'}]}, '4': {'Prompt': 'Tire', 'Response': [{'id': 2, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Used as weights ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:21:54.812Z'}, {'id': 3, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'A step', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:22:01.672Z'}, {'id': 4, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'A swing', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:22:09.414Z'}, {'id': 5, 'iid': 3, 'name': 'To grow potatoes in', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:22:28.885Z'}]}, '5': {'Prompt': 'Pants', 'Response': [{'id': 6, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Use instead of a handbag ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:23:55.376Z'}, {'id': 7, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Tie up the legs and grow vegetables in them', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:24:35.463Z'}, {'id': 8, 'iid': 2, 'name': 'A kite on a windy day', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:24:58.554Z'}]}, '6': {'Prompt': 'Bottle', 'Response': [{'id': 9, 'iid': 0, 'name': 'Flower vase', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:26:43.290Z'}, {'id': 10, 'iid': 1, 'name': 'Candle holder ', 'time': '2024-07-22T00:27:03.034Z'}]}, '7': {'HideTime': 0}, 'hitId': '668c95d8d24fe59d1423604a', 'feedback': {'q1': 'Somewhat easy', 'q2': 'More concerned than excited', 'q3': '4', 'q4': '100', 'q5': 'Thinking about what would fit in it', 'q6': ""Couldn't get snake to work""}, 'workerId': '664333b896d50fdfc656419d', 'assignmentId': '669da31932c7511c9f854205', 'ts_submitted_': '2024-07-22T00:29:42.456Z'}"
